<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Trufrost</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about">Professional chefs can now enjoy the benefits of reliable equipment built with reputed European refrigeration
        system &amp; controllers, high quality stainless steel and energy saving design with our products that include Refrigerated Reach-In
        Cabinets, Undercounters, Preparation Counters, Chef Tables, Saladettes, Countertop Displays, Blast Freezers &amp; Chillers and a
        complete range of Ice Cube Making Machines. Team Trufrost also has a proven expertise in design, supply and  installation of
        walk in coolers and freezers for commercial kitchens. \n \n
        Our Butler range of cooking products, coffee machines and blenders , food preparation and bakery products complement the Trufrost
        rangeof cooling products to comprehensively address the  foodservice equipment needs of commercial kitchens and coffee shops.</string>

    <string name="commercial_kitchens">Professional chefs can now enjoy the benefits of reliable equipment built with reputed European refrigeration
        system &amp; controllers, high quality stainless steel and energy saving design with our products that include Refrigerated Reach-In
        Cabinets, Undercounters, Preparation Counters, Chef Tables, Saladettes, Countertop Displays, Blast Freezers &amp; Chillers and a
        complete range of Ice Cube Making Machines. Team Trufrost also has a proven expertise in design, supply and  installation of
        walk in coolers and freezers for commercial kitchens. \n \n
        Our Butler range of cooking products, coffee machines and blenders , food preparation and bakery products complement the Trufrost
        rangeof cooling products to comprehensively address the  foodservice equipment needs of commercial kitchens and coffee shops.</string>

    <string name="bars_pubs">If you wish to set up a truly world class bar or a pub, Trufrost provides you a distinct advantage with its comprehensive
        bouquet of bar refrigeration products that include a fabulous range of wine coolers, bottle coolers, undercounter back bars and ice machines for
        those who care to stand out from the crowd. Team Trufrost also has a proven expertise in design, supply and  installation of wine walls and walk in coolers.
        Our Butler range of cooking products, coffee machines and blenders , food preparation and bakery products complement the Trufrost range of cooling products to
        comprehensively address the foodservice equipment needs of bars &amp; pubs.</string>

    <string name="cake_sweet_shop">With Trufrost Display Cases you can virtually upgrade your food business to club class. These world class showcases are built using
        reliable cooling system, controllers and design elegance that Europe is known for. In short, these are designed to increase your sales… not your problems.
        Team Trufrost also has a proven expertise in design, supply and  installation of walk in coolers and freezers.
        Our Butler range of cooking products, coffee machines and blenders , food preparation and bakery products complement the Trufrost range of cooling products to
        comprehensively address the food service equipment needs of cafes’, cake &amp; sweet shops.</string>

    <string name="food_retail">Trufrost presents a truly world class range of Coolers and Freezers for a wide variety of applications. You can choose between Upright
        and Chest type versions and capacities that range from 100 litres to 1000 litres. Trufrost also presents a truly high quality range of dispensers designed to
        help scale up the sales and profitability of ice cream parlours, frozen yogurt outlets, convenience stores, coffee shops,food courts, kiosks and a wide variety
        of small and medium sized stores. Team Trufrost also has a proven expertise in design, supply and installation of walk in coolers and freezers for larger applications.
        Our Butler range of cooking products, coffee machines and blenders , food preparation and bakery products complement the Trufrost range of cooling products to comprehensively
        address the food service equipment needs of food retail business. </string>

    <string name="food_preservation">Be it small walk-in coolers &amp; freezers, or large refrigerated warehouses, we specialize in preservation &amp; storage of products ranging
        from hospitality, frozen foods, fresh produce, dairy products, beverages, medicines &amp; vaccinations. Having worked in the cold chain industry for over 3 decades, Team
        Trufrost has done extensive work with leading brands like Accor, Hilton, Marriott, Taj Hotels, Subway, Sanofi, Johnson &amp; Johnson, Ranbaxy, Dinshaw’s, Radisson, Westin,
        Park Plaza, Haldiram’s, Ramada, Amul, ITC, Oberoi, Shantha Biotechnics, Radha Regent, Cisco and many more names.</string>

    <string name="bio_medical">Trufrost brings to India a comprehensive range of reliable biomedical refrigeration products suitable for hospitals, blood banks, pharmacies, research
        institutes, laboratories in electronic &amp; chemical plants, fisheries and more with products that include Ultra Low Temp Freezers, Pharmacy Freezers &amp; Coolers, Blood Bank
        Refrigeration, Mobile Coolers, Blood Platelet Incubators and Lab use Ice Flake Machines.
        Team Trufrost also has a proven expertise in design, supply and installation of walk in coolers and freezers for larger applications.</string>


    <string-array name="description">
        <item>@string/commercial_kitchens</item>
        <item>@string/bars_pubs</item>
        <item>@string/cake_sweet_shop</item>
        <item>@string/food_retail</item>
        <item>@string/food_preservation</item>
        <item>@string/bio_medical</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="commercial_kitchens_title">Commercial Kitchen</string>
    <string name="bars_and_pubs_title">Bar &amp; Pubs</string>
    <string name="cake_and_sweet_shops_title">Cake &amp; Sweet shops</string>
    <string name="food_retail_title">Food Retail</string>
    <string name="food_preservation_title">Food Preservation</string>
    <string name="bio_medical_title">Bio Medical</string>

    <!-- related to transition -->
    <string name="viewpager_transition">viewpager_transition</string>

    <!-- related to progress bar-->
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait&#8230;</string>
</resources>
